[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かぜ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Простуда"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅっちょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відрядження"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅっちょうします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відрядженняїхати у відрядження"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おだいじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Будь здоров, бережи себе"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どうしましたか' read in word?",
        "answer": "Що трапилось?"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とびます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Літати"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はこびます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Переносити, переставляти"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もどします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Повертати (на попереднє місце)"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ほし' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зірка"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひかり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Світ, блиск, промінь"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そら' read in word?",
        "answer": "Небо"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おと' read in word?",
        "answer": "Звук"
    }
]